Guide to the Howard Conklin papers, 1949-1982.
Conklin, Howard papers, 1949-1982.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Howard Conklin papers, 1949-1982.
21-10-2878
Howard E. Conklin.
21.3 cubic ft.
Correspondence, course material and class lecture notes, professional writings, extension surveys and followups, subject files, project statements, charts, graphs, and other materials.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Correspondence, course material and class lecture notes, professional writings, extension surveys and followups, subject files, project statements, material relating to Cornell University, and subject files relating to the New York State Land Use Committee and the New York State Agricultural Resource Commission. Also, charts, graphs, and other materials from the "Decade of the Sixties," study about changes in commercial farms in New York State.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Professor Emeritus, Agricultural Resources and Managerial Economics.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Correspondence, course material and class lecture notes, professional writings, extension surveys and followups, subject files, project statements, material relating to Cornell University, and subject files relating to the New York State Land Use Committee and the New York State Agricultural Resource Commission. Also, charts, graphs, and other materials from the "Decade of the Sixties," study about changes in commercial farms in New York State.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Conklin, Howard E.; Cornell University--Faculty.; New York (State) State Advisory Committee on Land Use Statistics.; New York (State) Agricultural Resources Commission.; New York State College of Agriculture. Dept. of Agricultural Resources and Managerial Economics.
Subjects:
Agriculture--Study and teaching.; Agricultural conservation.; Land use--New York (State)--Study and teaching.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- My Activities 1949-1963 (Box 1)
- My Activities 1963-1971 (Box 2)
- My Activities 1971-1977 (Box 3)
- My Activities 1977-1982 (Box 4)
- Course Materials (Box 5-6)
- Land Classification Photos by County (Box 7)
- Extension Followups in Counties (Box 8)
- Early class work and NYS Land Use Committee (Box 9)
- Old General Correspondence A-S (Box 10)
- Old General Correspondence S-Z; Newer General Correspondence A-L (Box 11)
- Newer General Correspondence M-Z; Foreign Correspondence A-Z; Extension Correspondence A-M (Box 12)
- Extension Correspondence M-Y; Campus Correspondence A-Z; Campus Administration A-Z (Box 13)
- Correspondence outside University 1960-1970 A-Z (Box 14)
- Annual Project Statements (Box 15)
- Annual Project Statements; Agricultural Resource Commission (Box 16)
- Agricultural Resource Commission (Box 17)
- Agricultural Resource Commission (Box 18)
- Unprocessed material (Box 19-22)